

## KARIN RAKSNAUGRAHA

Offline Film Editor, Based in Buckinghamshire, UK

Over five years of experience, utlising a vast variety of video and audio editing programmes to efficiently deliver emotional story-telling. Fully equipped and well experienced working remotely, if needed.

**EXPERIENCE** 

Mar2021 - present

Jul2021 - Aug2021

May2021 - Jun2021

Video Editor for Aerial.ie

Clipping and video file management in local systems and private and public online servers, cutting commercials for clients incl.

Irish Rail, Samsung, and Coca-Cola
Oct2021 - Nov2021 **Production Assistant** for *Maud Films* 

Reporting to 3rd AD, providing support on set to all departments

**Video Editing** for *Ambilhati Advertising Agency (internship)*As part of a resident team, editing commercial and promotional

content for clients incl. Disney+ Hotstar

**Production Assitant** for *Rock Against Homelessness*Assisting on set and operating secondary cameras

**CREDITS**Short Films

**'Le Ciné' dir. Fred Stanton (2024)** Animation National Film and Television School Production

'Guideprice 1100PCM 1 Bed Flat To Rent' dir. Jake Kuhn (2024) Drama National Film and Television School

'For Fathers' dir. Lewis Isbell (2024) Documentary National Film and Television School

'0808 801 0677' dir. Jenny Barruol (2024) Documentary National Film and Television School

'Gallardo' dir. Sean Diarmuid Giacomelli O'Dwyer (2021) Drama Griffith College Dublin

**'19/2019' dir. Ross O'Riordan (2020)** Documentary Griffith College Dublin

'Annabel Lee' dir. Ross O'Riordan (2020) Drama

Winner: Single-Take Challenge, Audience Award

'Come With Cold Water' dir. Karin Raksanugraha (2019) Drama Griffith College Dublin

All films listed above were cut on Avid Media Composer.

CREDITS, cont'd Micro Shorts

'Brushtroke Fever' (2019) 'Momentum' (2019) 'Frilled Gish' (2019)

**EDUCATION** 

**National Film and Television School** 

MA Editing

Buckinghamshire, UK *2024-present* 

**Griffith College Dublin** 

BA (Hons) Communications and Media Production Dublin, Ireland 2021-2022

**Griffith College Dublin** 

BA Film and Television Production Dublin, Ireland 2018-2021

**Jakarta Intercultural School** 

International Baccaleureate Diploma Jakarta Indonesia 2016-2017

**English** 

Fluent

**Bahasa Indonesia** 

Fluent (Mothertongue)

German

Intermediate (B1 Level)

Spanish

Basic

**Video and Audio Editing Softwares** 

Avid Media Composer Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe Final Cut

DaVinci Resolve

**Image Editing Softwares** 

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator **HTML and CSS Softwares** 

Adobe Dreamweaver